(Sheldon:)Are you still
mad at me?
(Leonard:)Yes, we missed our lecture,
we were almost arrested,
(Leonard:)and you got me locked
in a room with a man
(Leonard:)who forced his tongue down the
throat of a stuffed Wookiee.
(Sheldon:)Boy, some people are just
glass-half-empty.
(Leonard:)The glass is
empty, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)It's completely empty.
(Leonard:)If you gave that glass to a
man who was dying of thirst,
(Leonard:)he would be dead,
do you know why?
(Sheldon:)Before I answer,
was he a smoker?
(Sheldon:)I think you're looking
at this all wrong.
(Leonard:)Fine, then tell me
how I should be looking at it.
(Sheldon:)Well, not only did we go to
Skywalker Ranch, we got in.
(Sheldon:)No one we know
can say that.
(Sheldon:)And for all the times
you find me irritating,
(Sheldon:)today you got to watch
someone shoot me with a Taser.
(Leonard:)That part was pretty good.
(Leonard:)See?
(Leonard:)You did flop around a lot.
(Sheldon:)I'll take your word for it.